## **ANTHONY BATTINELLI**

Stamford, CT

Phone: 203-249-1460 | Email: tbj86@outlook.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/anthony-battinelli | Portfolio: https://tbgolfer86.github.io/Portfolio/

GitHub: https://github.com/tbgolfer86

#### SUMMARY

Critical thinking full stack web developer with a web development certificate from the University of Connecticut. Experience in front and back end design utilizing a combination of strong communication, collaboration, problem-solving, analytical, and organizational skills. Ability to pay strong attention to detail in a fast-paced and diverse team environment consistently creating solutions that exceed expectations.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Softwares/Platforms: VSCode, GitHub, Heroku, Slack, Zoom, Schwab Streetsmart Edge

Software Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Node.js, Express.js, React.js, SQL Databases

#### **PROJECTS**

Recipe Finder | https://github.com/tbgolfer86/Recipe-Finder

Link to Deployed Project https://tbgolfer86.github.io/Recipe-Finder/

- Application that fetches food and drink recipes based on ingredients selected by the user.
- Responsible for front end design and execution, Javascript functionality
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bulma Framework, 2 APIs

Recipe Finder | https://github.com/tbgolfer86/Recipe-Finder

Link to Deployed Project https://tbgolfer86.github.io/Recipe-Finder/

- Application that fetches food and drink recipes based on ingredients selected by the user.
- Responsible for front end design and execution, Javascript functionality
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bulma Framework, 2 APIs

Recipe Finder | https://github.com/tbgolfer86/Recipe-Finder

Link to Deployed Project https://tbgolfer86.github.io/Recipe-Finder/

- Application that fetches food and drink recipes based on ingredients selected by the user.
- Responsible for front end design and execution, Javascript functionality
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bulma Framework, 2 APIs

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Burning Tree Country Club**

Caddie

2018 – Present

Greenwich, CT

Integrated superior customer service with golf knowledge to deliver a quality and consistent on-course experience in an upscale private country club environment. Key Accomplishments:

- Advised members and guests of all ages and skill levels with on-course strategy and decision making to maximize their potential and achieve better results
- Requested by membership and golf staff for off-site competitive tournaments

- 2020 Women's Club Champion Caddie
- 2021 Men's Club Champion Caddie

# Assistant Golf Professional Burning Tree Country Club

2011 – 2017

Greenwich, CT

Utilized strong communication and critical thinking skills to provide superior customer service and junior golf instruction in a private country club environment.

Key Accomplishments:

- Collaborated with a team of 8 to provide high quality customer service
- Coordinated and scheduled tee times for over 200 golfing members
- Ensured accurate golf lesson scheduling for 4 other golf professionals
- Provided junior golf instruction in both 1-on-1 settings and groups of up to 20
- Established and maintained relationships with members by answering their questions and assisting them in a detail oriented manner
- Managed over \$150,000 in merchandise using the Jonas System Point-of-Sale software
- Edited monthly club newsletter
- Finished Top-10 on Metropolitan PGA Assistants Tour
- Attained TaylorMade and Titleist golf staff player sponsorships
- Earned eligibility for the PGA of America's Professional Golf Management Program by passing the Playing Ability Test

#### **EDUCATION**

**Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp Certificate:** University of Connecticut, Virtual May 2023 A 24 week intensive program focused on getting technical programming skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Node.js, Express.js, React.js, and SQL Databases.

**Bachelor's Degree in Economics:** University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT 2004 – 2009